Hello friends, in the fairs, there is a tower of
many health insurance companies along with CMC Hospital,
which is called TPA, that is,
Third Party Administrator,
and this is called cashless facility,
and if you have some step of health insurance,
then you people will
get a ticket absolutely free in CMC Hospital, you people will not have to pay a single rupee,
so friends, today we will
know
which health insurance
company tower is along with CMC Hospital in the bills, how do you people
have to click, how do you get the cashless facility,
which document will definitely be required, I will
give complete details, so today in this
video you people have to do computer war
and before starting, friends, I have
a small request for all of you, if
you have come to the channel for the first time, then you must subscribe to the channel
and press the bell icon and like this video as well, so
friends, let's start
this topic of yours, friends,
in the fairs, to get the cashless press of CMC Hospital through Hay Fever,
you people have to open some things  You definitely have to pay
attention and sister, you people
also have to understand this, see friends, in the bills
of CMC Hospital, even if we assume that
your patient has to see a doctor, get his
face examined, then he has to do tests
etc. and buy medicine, then he will
not get this facility here, that is, the
health insurance money will
not be available here, if your patient gets admitted, that is, he gets admitted,
after admission, all the expenses of the patient
like the bed cost of the patient, post
operation cost, after that dialysis post
cost and many other things, only then
you will get these facilities, that is, only when the
patient is admitted, you will get
encephalitis treatment and friends, there are
many other things, to
get this facility, to claim their health insurance,
CMC
Hospital searches for Justin Bieber in the crowd, then there is
a fear of getting the gate pass by saying
Access 03, you people have to go there
and after going there you people have to contact
where the opening and closing
time is but from ATM  It is open there from 10 am to 8 pm
and you should go there and
contact and see
friends, if your patient will be admitted,
you have to plan two to three days before the admission,
you have to go to the access counter two to three days before
and before going in a scooter, it is
very important for you to carry some documents with you like
Voter Card, Aadhar
Card, PAN Card for Indian identity, after that it is
very important to carry passport for international identity
and after that you have to carry a
photocopy as well and your health card, you have to carry
that card also with you,
after going there you will get the
registration form, after going there
you have to submit that form, if you face even a little
problem in filling up the form, then the
sir who is doing the access work there will
help you a lot, he will tell people
everything in detail how to do it, there will be no
problem, hence
you have to click two to three days before the admission of the doctor
After that, you will get it very easily through the cashless facility
and you will be
able to get treatment for free. And it is also very important that
friends,
if you get a delay in getting treatment through the cashless facility, that is, there is a
delay in getting the treatment done, then
you will have to pay the cost of the filler best thems
pistol.
After that,
for the responsibly comment, that is, to get the TPA,
you will have to go to the access account of CMC Hospital in the blood,
after that you will have to click for the arrangement and plan it
in the company.
You will have to get the return on Monday and
not to get the money back.
Sometimes delivery happens in the company, only then
you will have to make the payment. And after that,
see friends, if in the list that I will show you now,
if the
car you have is
not matching with this, that it will be a different car
and I will show in this list, it keeps
changing again and again.  It keeps changing,
so if you have a separate wire, it's
very important to go to your access computer and contact them, and it's possible
that common people will get clicked through you.
I'll list you guys right now,
and through the list, I'll
tell you which health insurance company towers are associated with CMC Hospital in the film.
Friends, in the comment section of this video, that is,
in the description box, I'll
give you details about the contact details for the response maintenance
department.
After that,
I'll give you the contact details for health insurance.
You can go there and contact them first. So,
friends, today we'll learn
which health insurance companies are associated with CMC Hospital in the film.
And to explain this, we'll take you to the
mobile screen. Friends,
look here it's written 'Health Insurance,'
and these are given below. Now you can see the
following TPS, Pace, and Black Insurance
Companies, and have been tagged with CMC, that is, all the
Black Insurance Companies listed below.
Team Hospital can manufacture it.
Look here, at number one it is
Withdrawal Health Care TPA Private
Limited, United Health Care India
Private Limited, Paramount Health Service
TPA Private Limited, Family Helpline
Limited, Medi Assist India Private
Limited, Heritage Health Service TV
Private Limited, Good Helpline Limited,
Park Mediclaim Consultants Private
Limited. After that, look at Indi India
Health Care Service Private Limited.
After that, let's go down a little and it is number nine. And
look, I have already
mentioned number nine. Look at number three it is
Pool Metro Private Limited, Met Se Health
Care TPA Limited, Met India Health Care
Tamil Nadu Government Employee Health
Insurance. Then there is Genius India TPA
Limited, Only for Kolkata Police. Then there is
MD India Health Care Tamil Nadu
Government Pencil Sharpener. Then there is Raksha
TPA Private Limited, Health Insurance
TPA of India Limited. Then there are
many more. Let me show you friends,
look, I told you about the
insurance companies earlier. And look, this is
not from a direct insurance company. Whatever I will
tell you now, all the companies I will
tell you have sexual relations with CMC, that is
That is ready, look at number 8 given here,
instead of
Germans Company Limited Star Health
Insurance Flight Insurance Company
Limited Cholamandalam MS General Insurance
Company Limited Vriddha
International Insurance Company Future
Generali India Insurance Company Limited,
after that come Free Mode Tokyo General
Insurance Company Limited
ICICI Lambert Lambert General Insurance then
Religare Health
Insurance Company Limited PCR General
Insurance Company Limited Reliance General Insurance Company Limited
Aditya Birla Health Insurance Company Limited
DSCR Health Insurance Company Limited,
after that let's go a little down,
after going down there are no more steps, that is,
total, which I have told you guys,
2019 Total Health Insurance
with Company Time and you should
not consider this list as the final list because the list keeps
changing sometimes and
changes happen again and again and it may be
related to the car you have
because changes keep happening, so
if you have some different government, then you can
take that car and contact the access point of CMC Hospital in the blood
in less time and it is possible
that your problem will be solved and you will get it
absolutely free  You will get tin bar for free, so
friends, let's go through some steps and update
here, friends, I hope you have got the
complete information and
understood everything, and friends, still
if you have even the slightest doubt regarding this, then
you can comment on it by going to the comment section of the bill,
and friends, anyway, if you
want to talk to me through chat,
want to ask that question, then you
can follow our instant remedy, the
idea of ​​Instagram is that medical solver and
you will get the link of Instagram ID in the description box of this point, so
friends, let's end today's video here,
see you in the next video
with the laptop, till then thank you so
much scholarship